雪橇铃儿响
Sleigh bells ring
你在听吗
Are you listening
乡间小道上
In the lane
积雪在闪烁
Snow is glistening
美景当前
A beautiful sight,
今晚我们玩得开心
We're happy tonight
走在这冬日的仙境里
Walking in a winter wonderland
蓝知更鸟飞走了
Gone away, is the blue bird
但又有新鸟在此停留
Here to stay, is the new bird
它唱着一首爱的歌谣
He sings a love song,
正如你我走在一起
As we go along
走在这冬日的仙境里
Walking in a winter wonderland
在雪地中我们堆个雪人
In the meadow we can build a snowman
注:
帕森布朗指神父帕森布朗，是这首民谣里的人物
想象他是帕森布朗
And pretend that he is Parson Brown
他会问我们结婚了吗
He'll say are you married
我们说没有
We'll say no man
但你能完成这项任务
But you can do the job
当你在城镇里的时候
When you're in town
后来
Later on
我们一起
We'll conspire
在火炉旁做梦的时候
As we dream by the fire
无忧无虑
To face unafraid
我们的计划
The plans that we've made
走在这冬日的仙境里
Walking in a winter wonderland
在雪地中我们堆个雪人
In the meadow we can build a snowman
想象他是马戏团的小丑
And pretend that he's a circus clown
和雪人先生玩得愉快
We'll have lots of fun with Mr. Snowman
直到别人推倒他
Until the other kiddies knock them down
下雪时
When it snows
不让人赞叹吗
ain't it thrilling
虽然这让你的鼻子感到寒冷
Though your nose, gets a chilling
我们像爱斯基摩人一样玩耍
We'll frolic and play, the Eskimo way
走在这冬日的仙境里
Walking in a winter wonderland